var chapters = [
  //   { chapter: 1, title: "Cost Accounting - An Introduction" },
  //   { chapter: 2, title: "Materials" },
  //   { chapter: 3, title: "Activity Based Costing" },
  { chapter: 4, title: "Budgetary Control" },
  { chapter: 5, title: "Cost Volume Relations & Break Even Analysis" },
  { chapter: 6, title: "Methods   of   Costing" },
  { chapter: 7, title: "Standard Costing  & Variance Analysis" },
  { chapter: 8, title: "Marginal Costing" },
];

var allQuestionAnswers = [
  {
    question:
      "A budgetary control system secures control over performance and costs in the different parts of a business by?",
    options: [
      "By establishing budgets",
      "By comparing actual attainments against the budgets",
      "By taking corrective action and remedial measure or revision of the budgets, if necessary",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "_______ is a blue print of the projected plan of action expresses in quantitative terms and for a specified period time?",
    options: ["Cost", "Balance sheet", "Budget", "None of the above"],
    answer: "Budget",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the objective of budgetary control?",
    options: [
      "To reduce losses and waste to the minimum",
      "To bring out clearly where effort is needed to remedy the situation",
      "To see that the firm is not deflected from marching towards its long- term objectives without being overwhelmed by emergencies",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "________ is statement defining functional representatives of executives responsible for accomplishment of organizational objectives?",
    options: [
      "Budget center",
      "Budget manual",
      "Organization chart",
      "Cost budget",
    ],
    answer: "Organization chart",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "_________ is a document which sets outstanding instructions governing the responsibilities of persons and the procedures?",
    options: [
      "Budget period",
      "Budget control",
      "Budget manual",
      "Budget center",
    ],
    answer: "Budget manual",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "_________ is described by CIMA London terminology as a factor which will limit the activities of an undertaking and which is taken into account in preparing budgets?",
    options: [
      "Budgets reports",
      "Budget key factors",
      "Budget controller",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Budget key factors",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A static budget is useful in controlling costs when cost behavior is:",
    options: ["Mixed", "Fixed", "Variable", "Linear"],
    answer: "Fixed",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "_______ is consolidated summary of the various functional budgets?",
    options: [
      "Principal budget",
      "Master budget",
      "Cash budget",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Master budget",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Flexible budget are prepared in which method?",
    options: [
      "Tabular method",
      "Formula method",
      "Graphic method",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "At 9,000 direct labor hours, the flexible budget for indirect materials is Rs27, 000. If Rs28,000 of indirect materials costs are incurred at 9,200 direct labor hours, the flexible budget report should show the following difference for indirect materials:",
    options: [
      "1,000 unfavorable.",
      "1,000 favorable",
      "400 favorable.",
      "400 unfavorable",
    ],
    answer: "400 unfavorable",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Under responsibility accounting, the evaluation of a manager’s performance is based on matters that the manager:",
    options: [
      "Directly controls",
      "Directly and indirectly controls",
      "Indirectly controls",
      "Has shared responsibility for with another manager",
    ],
    answer: "Directly controls",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "__________ budgeting is a revolutionary concept of planning the future activities and there is a sharp contradiction from conventional budgeting activities and there is a sharp contradiction from conventional budgeting?",
    options: [
      "Concept budgeting",
      "Zero base budgeting",
      "Performance budgeting",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Zero base budgeting",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Responsibility centers include:",
    options: [
      "Cost centers",
      "Profit centers",
      "Investment centers",
      "all of the above",
    ],
    answer: "all of the above",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Under responsibility accounting, the evaluation of a manager’s performance is based on matters that the manager:",
    options: [
      "Directly controls",
      "Directly and indirectly controls",
      "Indirectly controls",
      "Has shared responsibility for with another manager",
    ],
    answer: "Directly controls",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "At zero direct labor hours in a flexible budget graph, the total budgeted cost line intersects the vertical axis at Rs30, 000. At 10,000 direct labor hours, a horizontal line drawn from the total budgeted cost line intersects the vertical axis at RS 90,000. Fixed and variable costs may be expressed",
    options: [
      "30,000 fixed plus 6 per direct labor hour variable",
      "30,000 fixed plus 9 per direct labor hour variable",
      "60,000 fixed plus 3 per direct labor hour variable",
      "60,000 fixed plus 6 per direct labor hour variable",
    ],
    answer: "30,000 fixed plus 6 per direct labor hour variable",
    chapter: 4,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Sales is 200000 Rs and variable cost is 120000, find the P/V ratio?",
    options: ["10%", "20%", "30%", "40%"],
    answer: "40%",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Fixed cost is 100000Rs and P/V ratio is 40%, find out the break-even point?",
    options: ["100000", "200000", "250000", "300000"],
    answer: "250000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If profit is 60000 Rs and P/V ratio is 40% then what will be the margin of safety?",
    options: ["50000", "100000", "150000", "200000"],
    answer: "150000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A firm sells widgets for Rs14 each. The variable costs for each unit are Rs8. The contribution margin per unit is?",
    options: ["6", "8", "10", "12"],
    answer: "6",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The current sales price is $25 per unit and the current variable cost is $17 per unit. Fixed costs are $40,000. If the sales price is increased by $2, and all other costs remain unchanged, the break-even point in units will:",
    options: [
      "Increase by 1,000 units",
      "Decrease by 1,000 units",
      "Decrease by 2,000 units",
      "Decrease by 119 units (rounded to nearest unit)",
    ],
    answer: "Decrease by 1,000 units",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If a firm's margin of safety is 35% on sales of Rs200,000, then its margin of safety on sales of Rs300,000 will be (assume fixed costs, the variable cost per unit, and the sales price per unit do not change)?",
    options: ["105000", "170000", "100000", "35000"],
    answer: "170000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If the margin of safety is 40% of sales, which are Rs400, 000, the break-even point?",
    options: ["200000", "240000", "300000", "350000"],
    answer: "240000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Company A's fixed costs were Rs42, 000 its variable costs were Rs24, 000 and its sales were Rs80, 000 for the sale of 8,000 units. The company's break-even point in units is:",
    options: ["8,000", "5,000", "6,000", "7,000"],
    answer: "6,000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "____________ Analysis helps management in finding out the relationship of costs and revenue to profit?",
    options: [
      "Break even",
      "Cost volume profit",
      "ABC analysis",
      "None of them",
    ],
    answer: "Cost volume profit",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A joiner charges customer Rs15 per hour, each hour incurring an estimated variable cost of Rs6. Total fixed cost for next year is estimated at Rs6000 for clerical support and Rs3000 for rent of premises.What is the joiner's breakeven point?",
    options: ["10000", "15000", "22500", "5000"],
    answer: "15000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A bakery has a margin of safety of 40% and estimated sales revenue of Rs70 000.\nWhat is the bakery’s breakeven point?",
    options: ["32000", "42000", "52000", "62000"],
    answer: "42000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A business requires to sell 22 000 units in order to earn a target profit of Rs150 000. The contribution per unit is Rs15.What is the business’s breakeven point?",
    options: ["15000", "14000", "10000", "12000"],
    answer: "12000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A single product company has a contribution to sales ratio of 40%. Fixed costs amount to Rs90 000 per annum.The number of units required to break even is?",
    options: [
      "3000",
      "4500",
      "5000",
      "Impossible to calculate without further information",
    ],
    answer: "Impossible to calculate without further information",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "66)\tH Limited manufactures and sells two products - J and K. Annual sales are expected to be in the ratio of J: 1 K: 3. Total annual sales are planned to be Rs420 000. Product J has a contribution to sales ratio of 40% whereas that of product K is 50%. Annual fixed costs are estimated to be Rs120 000.The budgeted breakeven sales value (to the nearest Rs1000)?",
    options: ["196000", "253000", "255000", "200000"],
    answer: "253000",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "_________ is the difference between the actual sales and sales at break-even point, sales beyond break even volume brings in profits?",
    options: [
      "Margin of safety",
      "Total sales",
      "Profit volume ratio",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Margin of safety",
    chapter: 5,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "__________ may be defined as system of costing in which the elements of cost are accumulated separately for each job or work order undertaken by an organization?",
    options: [
      "Margin of safety",
      "Job costing",
      "Standard costing",
      "Marginal costing",
    ],
    answer: "Job costing",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "There are certain industries where two or more products of equal importance are simultaneously produced such products are regarded as?",
    options: [
      "Substitute products",
      "Joint products",
      "By products",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Joint products",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In automobile industry what could be the co products are?",
    options: ["Cars", "Buses", "Trucks", "All of the above"],
    answer: "All of the above",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the objectives of joint cost analysis?",
    options: [
      "Data for price fixation",
      "Data for price fixation",
      "Determination of profit and loss on each time",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cost of an incomplete job, i.e., a job on which some manufacturing operation is till due is termed as?",
    options: [
      "Raw material",
      "Finished goods",
      "Work in progress",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Work in progress",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "__________ costing is one form of application of the principles of job order costing?",
    options: [
      "Job costing",
      "Contract costing",
      "Terminal costing",
      "Both B and C",
    ],
    answer: "Both B and C",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "_____________ Method according to which cost data of production are collected according to the departments or processes and thereafter the total cost is divided by the quantity of production, to arrive at the cost per unit?",
    options: [
      "Batch costing",
      "Process costing",
      "Marginal costing",
      "Job order costing",
    ],
    answer: "Process costing",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If the quantum of loss is less than the determined percentage of normal loss, the difference is called?",
    options: ["Abnormal loss", "Abnormal gain", "Normal profit", "Normal loss"],
    answer: "Abnormal gain",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "________ represent the production of a process in terms of completed units?",
    options: [
      "Normal production",
      "Work in progress",
      "Equivalent production",
      "All of above",
    ],
    answer: "Equivalent production",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "__________ may be used in job types of plants, particularly where the product or the particular operations of the job are of a standardized nature?",
    options: [
      "Marginal costing",
      "Standard costing",
      "Process costing",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Standard costing",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "________ Clause is usually provided in the contract as a safeguard against any likely changes, in the change in the prices or utilization of material and labor?",
    options: [
      "Escalation",
      "Force majeure",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Escalation",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "_______ are defined as any saleable or usable value incidentally produced in addition to the main product.",
    options: ["Residual", "Waste", "Garbage", "By product"],
    answer: "By product",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If in an oil refinery crude oil is processed what could be the by product?",
    options: ["Sulfur", "Bitumen", "Chemical", "All of the above"],
    answer: "All of the above",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Abnormal process loss is calculated as?",
    options: [
      "Normal cost of normal output/Normal output * Units of abnormal loss",
      "Normal cost of normal output/Abnormal output * Units of abnormal loss",
      "Normal cost of abnormal output/Normal output * Units of abnormal loss",
      "Normal cost of normal output/Normal output * Units of abnormal profit",
    ],
    answer:
      "Normal cost of normal output/Normal output * Units of abnormal loss",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Abnormal gain is calculated as?",
    options: [
      "Normal cost of normal output/units of normal output* Units of abnormal effective",
      "Normal cost of normal output/units of normal output* 100",
      "Normal cost of normal output/units of normal input* Units of abnormal effective",
      "Normal cost of abnormal output/units of normal output* Units of abnormal effective",
    ],
    answer:
      "Normal cost of normal output/units of normal output* Units of abnormal effective",
    chapter: 6,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "ABC Company, a lounge chair manufacturer, uses a standard costing system. Each unit of a finished product contains 3 yards of cloth. However, there is unavoidable waste of 0.5 yards per unit of finished product that occurs when the cloth is cut for assembly. The cost of the cloth is Rs10 per yard. The standard direct material cost for cloth per unit of finished product is?",
    options: ["Rs 5", "Rs 10", "Rs 25", "Rs 35"],
    answer: "Rs 35",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Mahindra Company employs a standard cost system in which direct materials inventory is carried at standard cost. The company has established the following standard for the materials costs of one unit of product\nStandard Quantity 6 kg\nStandard price 7 Rs/kg\nStandard cost 42 Rs\nDuring June, the company purchased 165,000 Kg of direct material at a total cost of Rs1, 171,500. The company manufactured 25,000 units of product during June using 151,000 Kg of direct materials. (Note that this is the same data that was provided for the previous question.) The direct material quantity variance for June is?",
    options: [
      "7,000 favorable",
      "7,000 unfavorable",
      "7,100 favorable",
      "7,100 unfavorable",
    ],
    answer: "7,000 unfavorable",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'The "standard quantity allowed" is computed by multiplying the?',
    options: [
      "actual input in units by the standard output allowed",
      "actual output in units by the standard input allowed",
      "actual output in units by the standard output allowed",
      "standard output in units by the standard input al",
    ],
    answer: "actual output in units by the standard input allowed",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "MUKESH Company employs a standard cost system in which direct materials inventory is carried at standard cost. The company has established the following standard for the direct labor costs of one unit of product\nStandard quantity 1.3 hours\nStandard price 22RS/ per hour\nStandard cost 28.60 Rs\nThe total factory wages for June were Rs800, 000, 90 percent of which were for direct labor. The company manufactured 25,000 units of product during June using 32,000 direct labor hours. The direct labor rate variance for June is?",
    options: [
      "16,000 favorable",
      "16,000 unfavorable",
      "96,000 favorable",
      "96,000 unfavorable",
    ],
    answer: "16,000 unfavorable",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Material A has standard price per kg is 5 Rs, standards usage per unit is 7 kg, actual price per kg is 4.5 Rs, actual usage per unit is 8 kg, material price variance would be?",
    options: [
      "4 Rs adverse",
      "4 Rs favorable",
      "3.5 Rs adverse",
      "3.5 Rs favorable",
    ],
    answer: "4 Rs favorable",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What term can be defined as a means of assessing the difference between a predetermined amount and the actual amount?",
    options: [
      "Activity based costing",
      "Variance analysis",
      "Master budgeting",
      "Investment appraisal",
    ],
    answer: "Variance analysis",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Job X has standard hours worked 64.5, actual hours worked 61.25, standard wage rate is 4.15 Rs, actual wage rate 4.25 Rs, actual labor variance will be?",
    options: [
      "7.36 favorable",
      "6.13 adverse",
      "6.13 favorable",
      "13.49 favorable",
    ],
    answer: "7.36 favorable",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "The formula for the materials price variance is?",
    options: [
      "Standard price less actual price multiplied by standard quantity",
      "Standard hours less actual hours multiplied by actual quantity",
      "Standard price less actual price multiplied by actual quantity",
      "Standard materials quantity less actual quantity multiplied by standard price",
    ],
    answer: "Standard price less actual price multiplied by actual quantity",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A favorable labor variance combined with an adverse wage rate variance could be caused by?",
    options: [
      "Higher unemployment in local economy",
      "Introduction of performance related pay",
      "Cheaper raw materials imported due to exchange rate depreciation",
      "Cost cutting exercises implement by management",
    ],
    answer: "Introduction of performance related pay",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When analyzing sale variances, which of the following would not be an important factor?",
    options: [
      "Volume variance",
      "Recovery rate variance",
      "Selling price variance",
      "Mix variance",
    ],
    answer: "Recovery rate variance",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Job ABC has standard hours worked 28, actual hours worked 26.5, standard wage rate is 5.60 Rs, actual wage rate 6.05 Rs, actual labor efficiency variance will be?",
    options: [
      "9.08 favorable",
      "3.53 adverse",
      "11.93 adverse",
      "8.40 favorable",
    ],
    answer: "8.40 favorable",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Houghton Company maintains warehouses that stock items carried by its e-retailer clients. When one of Houghton's clients receives an order from an online customer, the order is forwarded to Houghton. Houghton then pulls the item from the warehouse, packs it and ships it to the customer. Houghton uses a predetermined variable overhead rate based on direct labor-hours. According to the company's records, 0.04 direct labor-hours are required to fulfill an order for one item and the variable overhead rate is $6.50 per direct-labor hour. During July, Houghton shipped 240,000 orders using 9,200 direct labor-hours. The company incurred a total of $58,880 in variable overhead costs. The variable overhead rate variance during July was?",
    options: [
      "920 favorable",
      "920 unfavorable",
      "2,600 favorable",
      "2,600 unfavorable",
    ],
    answer: "920 favorable",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "As per standard performance levels it takes 1 hour to produce 4 units. If the actual production is 12 units in 6 hours, then how many standard hours have been worked?",
    options: ["2", "3", "4", "6"],
    answer: "3",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Standards that do not allow for machine breakdowns or other work interruptions and that require peak efficiency at all times are known as?",
    options: [
      "budgeted standards",
      "ideal standards",
      "normal standards",
      "practical standards",
    ],
    answer: "ideal standards",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Oman Company reported a favorable materials price variance and an unfavorable materials quantity variance. Based on these variances, the company's cost accountant would most likely conclude that?",
    options: [
      "the actual cost per unit of materials was less than the standard cost per unit",
      "the actual usage of materials was less than the standard allowed",
      "more materials were purchased than were used",
      "more materials were used than were purchased",
    ],
    answer:
      "the actual cost per unit of materials was less than the standard cost per unit",
    chapter: 7,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "__________ costing is a costing method in which only variable costs are accumulated and cost per unit is ascertained only on the basis of variable costs?",
    options: [
      "Fixed costing",
      "Variable costing",
      "Labor costing",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Variable costing",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Marginal costing is also known as direct costing?",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a variable cost?",
    options: [
      "Interest payments",
      "Raw materials costs",
      "Property taxes",
      "All of the above are variable costs",
    ],
    answer: "Raw materials costs",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is an implicit cost?",
    options: [
      "The salary earned by a corporate executive",
      "Depreciation in the value of a company-owned car as it wears out",
      "Property taxes",
      "All of the above are implicit costs",
    ],
    answer: "Depreciation in the value of a company-owned car as it wears out",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "The contribution margin per unit is equal to the?",
    options: [
      "price of a good",
      "the difference between total revenue and total cost",
      "difference between price and average total cost",
      "difference between price and average variable cost",
    ],
    answer: "difference between price and average variable cost",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The law of diminishing returns begins at the level of output where?",
    options: [
      "marginal cost is at a minimum",
      "average variable cost is at a minimum",
      "average fixed cost is at a maximum",
      "none of the above is correct",
    ],
    answer: "marginal cost is at a minimum",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Short-run marginal cost is equal to?",
    options: [
      "the change in total cost divided by the change in output",
      "the change in total variable cost divided by the change in output",
      "the cost per unit of the variable input divided by the marginal product of the variable input",
      "all of the above",
    ],
    answer: "all of the above",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which are ways in which profit performance of a business can be improved?",
    options: [
      "By increasing volume",
      "By increasing selling price",
      "By decreasing variable costs",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Profit planning is the planning of future operations to attain maximum profit or to maintain a specified level of profit?",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "_______ costing is a principle whereby fixed as well as variable costs are allotted to cost units?",
    options: [
      "Absorption costing",
      "Variable costing",
      "Fixed costing",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Absorption costing",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "__________ is the difference between selling price and marginal cost?",
    options: ["Profit", "Contribution", "Fixed cost", "All of the above"],
    answer: "Contribution",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Profit emerges only after charging which costs?",
    options: [
      "Prime costs",
      "Variable cost",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Both A and B",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Contribution or gross margin is the difference between sales and the marginal cost of sales?",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the statement is true?",
    options: [
      "Selling price-variable cost=contribution",
      "Contribution – fixed cost= profit",
      "Fixed cost + profit = contribution",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
    chapter: 8,
    marks: 1,
  },
];
